{
    "subject": "Arthur_Sheekman",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Gloria_Stuart",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Sheekman is married to Gloria Stuart.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9702668786048889,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Arthur Sheekman and Gloria Stuart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9439499974250793,
            "question": "Name the person married to Gloria Stuart."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9267364740371704,
            "question": "Is Arthur Sheekman married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227808713912964,
            "question": "To whom was Arthur Sheekman married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9171110987663269,
            "question": "Who is married to Gloria Stuart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7454060316085815,
            "question": "Who is Arthur Sheekman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6876948475837708,
            "question": "What is the name of Gloria Stuart's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6645162105560303,
            "question": "Who is Gloria Stuart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4831662178039551,
            "question": "Are there any famous individuals associated with Arthur Sheekman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3174207806587219,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Arthur Sheekman's personal life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Sheekman is married to Gloria Stuart.",
            "html": "yago_9270_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous individuals associated with Arthur Sheekman?",
            "html": "yago_9270_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Gloria Stuart?",
            "html": "yago_9270_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Gloria Stuart's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_9270_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9270_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Arthur Sheekman was previously married to Gloria Stuart (29.txt), and they were married for 43 years before Arthur's death (43.txt). Additionally, the documents describe Gloria Stuart as Arthur's wife (13.txt, 85.txt, 11.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Arthur Sheekman was previously married to Gloria Stuart, and also provide the specific dates of their marriage (28 July 1934) and divorce (Arthur Sheekman's death on 12th Jan 1978). Therefore, the statement \"Arthur Sheekman is married to Gloria Stuart\" is supported by the information given."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}